[
    {
       "id":1,
       "question":"What is www an acronym for?",
       "answer":"World Wide Web"
    },
    {
       "id":2,
       "question":"What is the best channel on youtube?",
       "answer":"Tom Scott"
    },
    {
       "id":3,
       "question":"Is this discord server the best server?",
       "answer":"Yes"
    },
    {
       "id":4,
       "question":"Is porn acceptable to post in this server",
       "answer":"No"
    },
    {
       "id":5,
       "question":"What does DDoS stand for.",
       "answer":"Distributed Denial of Service"
    },
    {
       "id":6,
       "question":"RAT is an acronym, for what?",
       "answer":"Remote administration tool"
    },
    {
       "id":7,
       "question":"What is a 3 letter acronym for something that can bypass windows defender",
       "answer":"FUD"
    },
    {
       "id":8,
       "question":"If you type python into a terminal, how would you exit",
       "answer":"exit()"
    },
    {
       "id":9,
       "question":"Can you name the username of the owner of Hackforums.net",
       "answer":"Omniscient"
    },
    {
       "id":10,
       "question":"Is Robot the best member in the server",
       "answer":"Yes"
    }
 ]
